Guide to the Garrett Orr Papers, circa 1873-1994, bulk 1890s-1914, 1935-1965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sketches Series, 1930s-1960s and undated
  - Billboard and Poster Designs Subseries, 1940s-1962 and undated
    - Miscellaneous images
      - Foot High Caps (Box 36)
      - Product (Box 36)
      - Refreshes (Box 36)
      - Sell! (Box 36)
  - Non-Advertising Sketches Subseries, 1930s and undated
    - General
      - Abstract designs (Box 36)
      - Bird (Box 36)
      - Female figures, (6 folders) (Box 36)
      - Groups, (7 folders) (Box 36)
      - Interior of office (Box 36)
      - Landscapes
        - Bicycle and tree (Box 36)
        - Building (Box 36)
        - Lighthouse, (2 folders) (Box 36)
        - Sea (Box 36)
        - Seashore (watercolor) (Box 36)
        - Town (charcoal drawing) (Box 36)
        - Town (watercolor), (2 folders) (Box 36)
      - Male figures, (14 folders) (Box 36)
      - Still life, (3 folders) (Box 36)
      - Other sketches, (7 folders) (Box 37)
        Includes self-portraits, studies of female forms and backdrop art. Some items removed to Oversize Folders 7-9.
    - Periodical and book cover illustrations (Box 37)
      Includes covers for Mission to Mackinac, The Outlander, Sherman: Fighting Prophet, 1776 Revolution, Vanity Fair, 1933 and 1935.
- Oversize Materials
  Oversize folders 4, 5, 7, and 8 have been reboxed into Box 38.
  - Artists and Illustrators Series, undated
    - Wilkinson, J. Walter, undated (Opaperfolder 1)
      Includes three original oil paintings Wilkinson made for the OAAA campaign To Make a Long Story Short--Use Outdoor Advertising.
  - Sketches Series, 1947-1956 and undated
    - Billboard and Poster Designs Subseries, 1947-1956 and undated
      - Billboard proofs, 1947-1956 and undated (Opaperfolder 2)
        Images include Arcadian fertilizer, Allied Chemical, Cheer, Colgate, Craig, Drake's cookies, Ford, Hamm's beer, Heinz soup, Kenl Ration, Life Saver, Nash automobiles, Ritz crackers, and Universal range.
      - Poster designs, undated (Opaperfolder 3 and 6)
        Images include Alpine cigarettes, Arrow shirts, Bowery Savings Bank, Bufferin, Busch beer, Chesterfield cigarettes, Colgate, Dacron, Defense Bonds, Dime Savings Bank, Dristan, DuPont, Folex Herbicides, Fram filters, Gillette, Greater New York Relief Fund, Ipana, IPNA, I.W. Harper whiskey, Kodl, Kool cigarettes, Listerine, Lucky Strike, Mazola oil, Micrin mouthwash, Muriel cigars, People's Drug, Philip Morris Company, Polar ice cream, Rexall Drug, Schenley Reserve whiskey, Teem, TESTA car, Trommers beer, Verney fabrics, Viceroy cigarettes, White Rose tea and outdoor advertising industry promotion.
      - Poster designs, undated (Box 38)
        Additional posters; see above for content.
    - Non-Advertising Sketches Subseries, 1962 and undated
      - Other Sketches, 1962 and undated (Opaperfolder 9)
        Includes landscapes, still life and form studies, portraits.
      - Other Sketches, undated (Box 38)
        Additional sketches, see above for content.